{
    "subject": "resource/Ron_Fenton",
    "predicate": "ontology/team",
    "object": "resource/Birmingham_City_F.C.",
    "human_readable": "Ron Fenton plays for Birmingham City F.C.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9783415794372559,
            "question": "When did Ron Fenton start playing for Birmingham City F.C.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6109674572944641,
            "question": "What league does Birmingham City F.C. play in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6060034036636353,
            "question": "Where is Birmingham City F.C. located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5801847577095032,
            "question": "What position does Ron Fenton play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5645853281021118,
            "question": "What football club does Ron Fenton play for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35270097851753235,
            "question": "Has Ron Fenton ever played for another team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31429314613342285,
            "question": "What is the name of Ron Fenton's home town?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2592521011829376,
            "question": "Is Ron Fenton a professional footballer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16093401610851288,
            "question": "Is Ron Fenton known for any particular skills or achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14756932854652405,
            "question": "Has Ron Fenton won any individual awards during his career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ron Fenton plays for Birmingham City F.C.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3345_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ron Fenton known for any particular skills or achievements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3345_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ron Fenton a professional footballer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3345_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Ron Fenton's home town?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3345_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3345_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3345_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3345_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3345_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3345_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3345_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3345_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3345_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3345_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3345_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that it contains two documents about a person named Ronald (Ron) Fenton. Here is the result:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention Ron Fenton playing for Birmingham City F.C."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document mentions that Ronald Fenton played for Birmingham City, which supports the statement that he played for Birmingham City F.C."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context about Ron Fenton playing for Birmingham City F.C. before his stint with Brentford, contradicting the statement.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}